{
    "id": "f90a90c82f354bc18c7fcc4b24fcdefd",
    "title": "Other vs. Another",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b278119db50e4f5ca6f5ca7da59f8813",
            "title": "Other vs. Another",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can I have .................................. cup of coffee?",
                    "description": "Another means additional or extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They looked at each ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You take this and I will take the ......................................... one.",
                    "description": "Other means one that is different or distinct from one that has already been mentioned.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must love one .............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ...................................... people have arrived.",
                    "description": "Other means one that is different or distinct from one that has already been mentioned.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Many .......................................... have also come.",
                    "description": "We use the plural form others after many.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will never get ........................................... chance.",
                    "description": "Another means additional or extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "One man's meat is ........................................ man's poison.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw her ........................................ day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "the other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the .................................... woman?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will take the …………………………. shirt.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They have bought ………………………… flat in Dubai.",
                    "description": "Another means an extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}